[
    {
        "question": "Which archipelago means `sheep islands`?",
        "answer": "Faroe Islands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does the largest snowball tournament in the world take place?",
        "answer": "Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two US states are separated by the Delaware Bay?",
        "answer": "Delaware and New Jersey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state is located between Maine and Vermont?",
        "answer": "New Hampshire"
    },
    {
        "question": "What old Massachusetts town is nicknamed `Witch city`?",
        "answer": "Salem"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ocean contains the spot where 0\u00b0 longitude meets 0\u00b0 latitude?",
        "answer": "Atlantic Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Canadian province is home to Pink Mountain, Muncho Lake and Nootka Sound?",
        "answer": "British Columbia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What fashionable shopping avenue divides New York into East Side and West Side?",
        "answer": "Fifth Avenue"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Quebec city does Canada`s capital border?",
        "answer": "Gatineau"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the highway that travels through all ten Canadian provinces?",
        "answer": "Trans-Canada Highway, or Route Transcanadienne"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river separates the cities of Detroit and Windsor?",
        "answer": "The Detroit River"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in France?",
        "answer": "Blanc"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Japan?",
        "answer": "Fuji"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Australia?",
        "answer": "Kosciusko"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Russia?",
        "answer": "Elbrus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Canada?",
        "answer": "Logan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Argentina?",
        "answer": "Aconcagua"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the river Ganges?",
        "answer": "Bangladesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the Yukon river?",
        "answer": "US"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the river Rhine?",
        "answer": "The Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the Dnieper river?",
        "answer": "Ukraine"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the Salween river?",
        "answer": "Myanmar"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the Orinoco river?",
        "answer": "Venezuela"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only landlocked country in Southeast Asia?",
        "answer": "Laos"
    },
    {
        "question": "Equity State is the official nickname of which state?",
        "answer": "Wyoming"
    },
    {
        "question": "What mountain is the tallest point in Turkey?",
        "answer": "Ararat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quito is the capital of which South American country?",
        "answer": "Ecuador"
    },
    {
        "question": "What town is Oklahoma State University located in?",
        "answer": "Stillwater"
    },
    {
        "question": "What continent is located at Latitude 90\u00b0 S Longitude 0.00\u00b0 E?",
        "answer": "Antarctica"
    },
    {
        "question": "Acapulco is a city in which Mexican state?",
        "answer": "Guerrero"
    },
    {
        "question": "The ancient Phoenician city of Constantine is located in what modern-day Arab country?",
        "answer": "Algeria"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year was the former republic of Czechoslovakia formed?",
        "answer": "1918"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Asian capital used to be called Peking?",
        "answer": "Beijing"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country are you likely to hear the cheer or toast `Opa!` during a celebration?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a calm ocean region near the equator called?",
        "answer": "Doldrums"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are you, if you landed at Lindberg Airport?",
        "answer": "San Diego"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Central American country extends farthest north?",
        "answer": "Belize"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which Chinese city is the Terracotta Army?",
        "answer": "Xian"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country is directly north of the continental United States?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Pennsylvania?",
        "answer": "Harrisburg"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Simi Valley is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "What desert is home to the Saguaro Cacti?",
        "answer": "Sonoran Desert"
    },
    {
        "question": "Miami is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "None, Miami is not a capital city"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river flows along the western border of Illinois?",
        "answer": "Mississippi River"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Rio Grande River flows in what body of water?",
        "answer": "Gulf of Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Battle of Gettysburg occurred in which US state?",
        "answer": "Pennsylvania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gouda and Edam are cities in what country?",
        "answer": "The Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only Asian country whose common name is only one syllable?",
        "answer": "Laos"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only African country whose common name is only one syllable?",
        "answer": "Chad"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country is Africa`s northernmost point?",
        "answer": "Tunisia"
    }
]